Yes, I slept in my lipstick. Every time I hear black folks reference the struggles we've been
through and our oppression as a reason to not care about other people, I feel like I'm hearing
the echoes of Zionism, i.e. we went through the Holocaust so we can harm whoever we want.
And we had the Holocaust so we can do whatever we want. I want you to know that's how you sound.
And I'll tell you that the black people that I'm from, that ain't how we get down. The sooner we black
folks start understanding ourselves as indigenous people and not just in the way where y'all be
like, we are indigenous so we're not slaves. No, that's not what I'm talking about. I'm talking
about seeing ourselves as a people of the earth, of the soil, and what comes along with
that. When we do that, we will be free. When we do that in the Caribbean, when we do that
here in the United States, when we do it everywhere, we will be free. Because we are the soil. And the soil
will take care of everybody. And everything.
Streets of Billfest in the dark of early morn.
See you next time.
Hey James.
Excuse me.
Thanks.
Hey James.
Hey James, what you guys believe this is for us?
Go quickly, man.
Thanks to Evidence, please.
Give us a chance.
How are youánd数 decir?